I'm Peppa Pig
and this is my little brother, George
This is Mummy Pig
and this is Daddy Pig
I'm Peppa Pig
"Windy Autumn Day"
Today, Peppa and her family are going to the park
It's very cold
It certainly is
Come on, put your warm clothes on
On cold days
Peppa and her family
wear hats, scarves, and coats
Let's put the roof up
And turn the heater on
Is everyone nice and warm?
-Yes, Daddy
Off we go, then
Here is the park
We're here!
-Hooray!
Mummy
why are all the leaves red and yellow?
Because it's autumn
In autumn, the weather gets colder
and the leaves change colour
It's quite windy
Let's play a game to keep warm
My turn!
Oh, the ball shouldn't go that way
The wind is blowing the ball away
The ball fell into the pond
I'll fish it out with this stick
Reach further, Daddy
Careful, Daddy Pig
Don't worry, almost got it
Daddy, is the water in the pond cold?
A little bit
The wind blew the ball out of the pond
That was lucky!
Yes
We're very lucky
It's getting windier now
Hold on to your hats
Oh dear
The wind blew George's hat away
Don't worry, George
Daddy will get your hat back for you
Go on, Daddy
Look
The hat is up in the tree
Let me climb up and fetch it
This tree is too thin
It won't hold your weight, Daddy Pig
How will we get George's hat back then?
Easy, I'll just shake the tree
Maybe I should shake it a bit harder
I thought that sort of thing only happened to me
It's not funny at all
It is quite funny, Mummy
I suppose it is a bit funny
George, where's your hat?
It's right on your head
Here's your hat, George
Hold onto it tightly this time
The wind has blown all the leaves off the trees
Look at me
The wind is holding me up
The wind is strong enough to hold Peppa up
The wind is strong enough to hold George up
You try it too, Daddy
I might be a bit too heavy
Come on, Daddy
It's really fun
Oh, all right then
The wind is even strong enough to hold Daddy Pig up
This is lots of fun
Mummy, come on
You try it too
If the wind stops, I'll fall down
The wind won't stop suddenly
The wind has stopped
It's not funny at all
But it is really funny
Now that the wind has stopped
what should we do?
What's your favourite game?
Jumping up and down in muddy puddles
But there aren't any muddy puddles here
There are only dry, boring leaves everywhere
So what are dry leaves good for?
I don't know
Jumping up and down on them
Daddy Pig loves jumping up and down in the leaves
Peppa loves jumping up and down in the leaves
Everyone loves jumping up and down in the leaves
This is the best autumn day ever